{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179243004","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179243004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 567dede7-f0f2-4811-b23e-4343ce3d5ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKA"," userResponse":" MKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179245695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179245695"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 567dede7-f0f2-4811-b23e-4343ce3d5ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179247253","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179247253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 567dede7-f0f2-4811-b23e-4343ce3d5ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179250615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179250615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 567dede7-f0f2-4811-b23e-4343ce3d5ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179251566","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179251566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 567dede7-f0f2-4811-b23e-4343ce3d5ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKO"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179252171","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179252171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 567dede7-f0f2-4811-b23e-4343ce3d5ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKO"," userResponse":" MKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179253322","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179253322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 567dede7-f0f2-4811-b23e-4343ce3d5ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179253423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179253423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 567dede7-f0f2-4811-b23e-4343ce3d5ee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKO"," userResponse":" MKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179265145","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179265145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKA"," userResponse":" MKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179268294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179268294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179269892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179269891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179273115","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179273114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179274687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179274687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKI"," userResponse":" MKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179278307","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179278306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179279919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179279919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKO"," userResponse":" MKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179283236","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179283236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179284843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179284842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKU"," userResponse":" MKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179288554","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179288553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179290581","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179290581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179290732","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179290732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179296131","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179296130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c46f0bc7-e39d-46cf-a708-ba8458ff9655"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mka..mku.asc.lc.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179306541","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179306541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c426022b-8763-462e-b5f1-2187e493f803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mko_ku-twi-mko"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mko"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179323006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179323006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c426022b-8763-462e-b5f1-2187e493f803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mko_tu-mko-ndi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mko"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179328840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179328840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c426022b-8763-462e-b5f1-2187e493f803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mko_mko-pu-to"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mko"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179345376","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179345376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c426022b-8763-462e-b5f1-2187e493f803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mko_mko-he-hu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mko"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179350105","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179350105"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c426022b-8763-462e-b5f1-2187e493f803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mko_ti-tha-mko"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mko"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179354935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179354935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c426022b-8763-462e-b5f1-2187e493f803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mko_po-nchi-mko"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mko"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179359956","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179359956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c426022b-8763-462e-b5f1-2187e493f803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mko_jo-mko-mno"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mko"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179365841","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179365841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c426022b-8763-462e-b5f1-2187e493f803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mko_yu-mko-le"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mko"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179390830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179390830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c426022b-8763-462e-b5f1-2187e493f803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mko_mko-mli-mwu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mko"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179395543","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179395543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c426022b-8763-462e-b5f1-2187e493f803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mko_she-mko-sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mko"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179401284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179401283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" c426022b-8763-462e-b5f1-2187e493f803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mko..mko.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mko_she-mko-sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179408547","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179408547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" b4ccc26c-8b10-49f4-95f9-d793fec40e76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179428838","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179428837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" b4ccc26c-8b10-49f4-95f9-d793fec40e76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179431773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179431772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" b4ccc26c-8b10-49f4-95f9-d793fec40e76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179431842","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179431842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" b4ccc26c-8b10-49f4-95f9-d793fec40e76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179441667","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179441667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndu_ndu-chi-nyi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndu"," userResponse":" ndu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179446978","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179446978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_mgo-mke-mki"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179455118","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179455118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_thi_njo-swa-thi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" thi"," userResponse":" thi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179471158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179471158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mta_nji-mno-mta"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mta"," userResponse":" mta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179477602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179477602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mzu_mme-dha-mzu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mzu"," userResponse":" mzu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179483514","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179483514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpi"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179490035","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179490035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpi"," userResponse":" mpi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179495124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179495124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179500745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179500745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mgu_nje-nja-mgu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mgu"," userResponse":" mgu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179505647","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179505646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nja_mwo-vya-nja"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179510429","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179510429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_bwa-nji-mfa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179516190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179516190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_bwa-nji-mfa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179522442","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179522442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 4f220014-320c-4fa5-ac22-8b5191d7ce35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_bwa-nji-mfa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179533564","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179533564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179533964","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179533963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179534209","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179534208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179534539","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179534538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179534781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179534780"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179538295","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179538294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179538597","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179538596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179539519","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179539518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179539953","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179539952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179542918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179542917"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179543216","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179543215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179544065","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179544064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179544749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179544748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179545499","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179545499"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179545849","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179545849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179546130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179546130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179546453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179546453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179546726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179546726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179550461","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179550461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179550855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179550855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179551101","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179551100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179551429","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179551428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179551673","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179551672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179555146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179555146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179555450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179555449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179556366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179556365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179556798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179556797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179559762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179559762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179560053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179560052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179560907","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179560906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179561580","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179561579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179562326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179562325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179562662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179562661"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179562949","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179562949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179563270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179563269"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179563543","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179563542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179567007","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179567006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179567118","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179567117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 3d52fd14-bfa2-41d4-aed1-d45f16ea798c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179578278","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179578278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 52874347-9de3-4ab3-9600-001d48c0434a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-3-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179583017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179583017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 52874347-9de3-4ab3-9600-001d48c0434a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-11"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179588159","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179588159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 52874347-9de3-4ab3-9600-001d48c0434a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_13-12-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179594306","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179594306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 52874347-9de3-4ab3-9600-001d48c0434a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-13-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179599790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179599790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 52874347-9de3-4ab3-9600-001d48c0434a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_10-11-12"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179605550","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179605550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 52874347-9de3-4ab3-9600-001d48c0434a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-5-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179611244","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179611243"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 52874347-9de3-4ab3-9600-001d48c0434a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179615794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179615794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 52874347-9de3-4ab3-9600-001d48c0434a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-13"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179619935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179619934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 52874347-9de3-4ab3-9600-001d48c0434a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179625528","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179625528"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 52874347-9de3-4ab3-9600-001d48c0434a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179630543","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179630543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 52874347-9de3-4ab3-9600-001d48c0434a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179637050","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179637050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 52874347-9de3-4ab3-9600-001d48c0434a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179658015","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179658015"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nda_di_mpa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179664689","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179664689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_le_chi_nda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179671317","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179671316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kha_nyo_nda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179677966","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179677966"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nda_sho_nu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179684617","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179684617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_wu_nda_ta"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179691294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179691294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mno_fe_nda"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179697955","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179697954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mo_sho_nda"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179704614","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179704614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nda_msta_wa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179711293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179711293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nda_bwe_kwa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179717961","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179717959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179731153","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179731153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179737857","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179737856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179746172","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179746171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179780727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179780725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179787653","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179787652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179794034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179794034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179805136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179805136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179811091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179811091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179818730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179818730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179824240","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179824239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 0641c3b0-3b00-4fa2-9f59-009d53047d53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179836817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179836816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 700d2b1f-cccf-43d7-b79e-db3b31ed5d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-cha-mme"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179842724","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179842724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 700d2b1f-cccf-43d7-b79e-db3b31ed5d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ho-mme-mcho"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179847301","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179847300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 700d2b1f-cccf-43d7-b79e-db3b31ed5d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mme-bi-mbi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179852540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179852540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 700d2b1f-cccf-43d7-b79e-db3b31ed5d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_fi-ta-mme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179857383","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179857382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 700d2b1f-cccf-43d7-b79e-db3b31ed5d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ng'o-ve-mme"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179861909","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179861909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 700d2b1f-cccf-43d7-b79e-db3b31ed5d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-po-mme"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179867524","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179867524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 700d2b1f-cccf-43d7-b79e-db3b31ed5d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-po-mme"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179873584","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179873584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 700d2b1f-cccf-43d7-b79e-db3b31ed5d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-mme-no"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179878076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179878076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 700d2b1f-cccf-43d7-b79e-db3b31ed5d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-mme-ze"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179883083","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179883083"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 700d2b1f-cccf-43d7-b79e-db3b31ed5d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mwo-mme-vi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179887911","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179887911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 700d2b1f-cccf-43d7-b79e-db3b31ed5d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_nji-mko-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179893665","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179893664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 700d2b1f-cccf-43d7-b79e-db3b31ed5d49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_nji-mko-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179906455","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179906455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mwo-mme-vi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mwo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179912914","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179912914"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mwo-mme-vi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179918090","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179918089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-mme-no"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179926282","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179926282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ho-mme-mcho"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179934441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179934441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ng'o-ve-mme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179940398","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179940398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mme-bi-mbi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179949643","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179949643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-po-mme"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179958445","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179958444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_nji-mko-mme"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179964118","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179964118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-mme-ze"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179968790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179968790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_fi-ta-mme"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179973709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179973709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-cha-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179979457","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179979457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-cha-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179988081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179988081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-cha-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549179996270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549179996270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-cha-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180003757","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180003757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-cha-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180012769","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180012769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 32bf4ffb-70da-46b0-9968-f5f92feee800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-cha-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180023586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180023586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-cha-mme"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180028906","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180028906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-mme-ze"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180036681","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180036681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ng'o-ve-mme"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180042056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180042055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-po-mme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180054332","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180054332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-po-mme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180059561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180059561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_fi-ta-mme"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" fi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180067866","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180067866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_fi-ta-mme"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180075573","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180075573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-mme-no"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" no"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180081223","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180081223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-mme-no"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180086518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180086518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mme-bi-mbi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180092468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180092468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_nji-mko-mme"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180100631","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180100631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mwo-mme-vi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180117985","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180117985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ho-mme-mcho"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180123739","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180123738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ho-mme-mcho"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180132383","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180132383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ho-mme-mcho"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180142590","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180142589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ho-mme-mcho"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180147848","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180147848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 2001d40e-b7b2-475f-a717-1c00bff4e829"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ho-mme-mcho"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180157382","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180157382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180158413","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180158413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMA"," userResponse":" MMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180161135","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180161135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180162184","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180162184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MME"," userResponse":" MME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180165797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180165796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180166849","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180166849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMI"," userResponse":" MMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180170387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180170387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMO"," userResponse":" MMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180171419","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180171418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMO"," userResponse":" MMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180175232","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180175232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMU"," userResponse":" MMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180176266","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180176266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMU"," userResponse":" MMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180179974","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180179973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180180069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180180069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMU"," userResponse":" MMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180185240","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180185240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 71e23a8b-c5a7-439c-a938-7012c2f83711"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180195709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180195709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" fcc0db99-e29b-4f88-bdf1-1f2c86a86e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mzu_mme-dha-mzu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mzu"," userResponse":" mzu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180200289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180200289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" fcc0db99-e29b-4f88-bdf1-1f2c86a86e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nja_mwo-vya-nja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180205022","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180205022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" fcc0db99-e29b-4f88-bdf1-1f2c86a86e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_bwa-nji-mfa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180209279","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180209279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" fcc0db99-e29b-4f88-bdf1-1f2c86a86e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndu_ndu-chi-nyi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndu"," userResponse":" ndu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180213884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180213884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" fcc0db99-e29b-4f88-bdf1-1f2c86a86e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpi"," userResponse":" mpi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180218925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180218925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" fcc0db99-e29b-4f88-bdf1-1f2c86a86e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mta_nji-mno-mta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mta"," userResponse":" mta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180223908","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180223908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" fcc0db99-e29b-4f88-bdf1-1f2c86a86e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_thi_njo-swa-thi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" thi"," userResponse":" thi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180228706","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180228705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" fcc0db99-e29b-4f88-bdf1-1f2c86a86e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180233431","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180233431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" fcc0db99-e29b-4f88-bdf1-1f2c86a86e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_mgo-mke-mki"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180238355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180238355"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" fcc0db99-e29b-4f88-bdf1-1f2c86a86e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mgu_nje-nja-mgu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mgu"," userResponse":" mgu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180244134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180244133"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" fcc0db99-e29b-4f88-bdf1-1f2c86a86e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mgu_nje-nja-mgu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180251506","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180251506"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" fcc0db99-e29b-4f88-bdf1-1f2c86a86e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mgu_nje-nja-mgu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180263026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180263026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-ku-mbe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180268433","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180268433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_mwe-kwu-mla"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180272840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180272840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-sho-yu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180277546","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180277546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_nyu-kwu-re"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180282354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180282354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ngu-swa-kwu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180286556","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180286556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-po-yu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180292650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180292650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_du-kwu-vyi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180297322","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180297321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_la-kwu-gi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180301627","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180301627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ng'e-kwu-te"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180396515","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180396515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ga-la-kwu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180402282","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180402281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ga-la-kwu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180411786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180411786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ga-la-kwu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.70","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180421455","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180421455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ga-la-kwu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180428764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180428764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_103344"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ga-la-kwu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}